嘿，你们帮我一下，好吗?
- Hey you guys give me a hand will ya?
-你知道你在干什么吗?
- What the hell do you think you're doing, huh?
嗯?
Huh?
——等等!
- Hold it!
——看!
- Watch it!
——出去!
- Get out!
滚出去!
Get out!
快跑!快跑!
Run! Run!
加油，加油!
Come on, come on!
你这个…
You son of a...
-天啊。
- Oh my god.
瑞秋，这是丹。
Rachel, this is Dan.
第十孔。
10th hole.
发生了一起谋杀案。
There's been a murder.
你最好叫警察过来，快点!
You better get the cops out here, quick!
所有西区单位:
All West Side units:
市政高尔夫球场可能有4 -51。
Possible four-51 at municipal golf course.
立即响应。
Respond immediately.
-副本。
- Copy.
高尔夫球场4比51。
Four-51 at the golf course.
我们走吧!
Let's go!
-把枪拿来。
- Get the gun.
放开这狗娘养的!
Off the son of a bitch!
-所有单位，所有单位。
- All units, all units.
我们在西湖市政高尔夫球场有一个10-20。
We have a 10-20 at western lake municipal golf course.
谨慎行事。
Proceed with caution.
重复一遍，小心行事。
I repeat, proceed with caution.
结束了。
Over.
-收到，我们马上就到。
- 10-four, we're on our way.
-他在那儿!-别开枪。
- There he is! - Hold your fire.
-我没人能击中那架直升机。
- I don't anyone to hit that chopper.
-坚持住，我去找他!
- Hold on, I'll get him!
-叫急救人员过来!
- Call the paramedics in here!
-把他们俩从水里弄出来!
- Get these two out of the water!
他一定在水里。
He must be in the water.
看出来。
Look out.
嘿,这里!
Hey over here!
他去!
There he goes!
-你们快点!
- You guys hurry up!
你们快下来!
You guys come on down here!
-过来!
- Come on over here!
我有他。
I've got him.
他是在这里!
He's right here!
别动，别动!
Hold it there, hold it!
了他!
Got him!
-怎么了?
- What's going on?
-他去哪了?
- Where'd he go?
他到底去哪儿了?
Where the hell did he go?
-他不是刚来过吗?
- Weren't he just here?
——该死的!
- Damn!
让我们找到这家伙!
Let's find this dude!
来吧!
Come on!
散开，我们去抓他!
Spread out, let's get him!
-我们走，快点。——加油!
- Let's go, come on. - Come on!
呆在一起!
Stay together!
我的心和灵魂都在发烧
J“ there's a fever running through my heart and soul j“
太渴望有人带我回家了
j“ so hungry for someone to take me home j“
J "爱咬。"
j“ love bites j“
j“我可以在夜晚品尝它。”
j“ I can taste it in the night j“
我需要一个爱人
j“ I need a lover j“
J "爱咬。"
j“ love bites j“
j“我得满足我的食欲。”
j“ I've got to feed my appetite j“
给我找个爱人
j“ find me a lover j“
j“我一直在等。”
j“ I've been waiting j“
J "代表爱情的完美结合
j“ for the striking of the match of love j“
会带我去的人
j“ someone who'll take me j“
跳下我的脚，奔向欲望的热度
j“ off my feet and to the heat of desire j”
我还能坚持多久
j“ how much longer can I keep on holding on j“
来个人救救我吧
j“ someone come and rescue me j“
j“我快要走了。”
j“ I'm almost gone j“
你还好吗?
Are you alright?
需要帮忙吗?
Do you need any help?
哦,上帝!
Oh god!
-你没看到任何武器吗?
- You didn't see any kind of a weapon?
连枪或刀都没有吗?
Not even a gun or a knife?
——没有。
- No.
也许躺在附近?
Lying nearby maybe?
-我告诉过你。
- I told you.
我找到他的时候他已经死了。
He was dead when I found him.
-但你确定吗?
- But are you sure?
-我没检查他
- I didn't examine him.
看在上帝的份上，我不是急救人员。
I'm not a paramedic for Christ sakes.
这到底是什么?
What is this anyway?
冷静下来。
Calm down.
-这个人谋杀了一位非常重要的科学家，杀了保安，警察，而我们对他一无所知。
- Now, this man murdered a very important scientist, killed security guards, police men, and we know nothing about him.
-饶了她吧，中尉。
- Give her a break lieutenant.
对吧?
Alright?
——嗯,好吧。
- Yeah, okay.
赖德小姐，你可以走了。
Look, miss Ryder, you may go now.
你们保持联系。
You keep in touch.
-艰难的一天，是吧?
- Rough day, huh?
-谢谢，但我不喝软饮料。
- Yeah, thanks, but I don't use soft-drinks.
来点咖啡怎么样?
- How about some coffee?
——没有。
- No.
——威士忌?
- Whiskey?
代基里酒吗?
A daiquiri?
——对不起。
- Sorry.
——披萨?
- Pizza?
墨西哥煎玉米卷吗?
Taco?
来点糖果怎么样?
How about some candy?
你还好吗?
Are you alright?
-我没事。
- Yeah I'm okay.
我只想一个人待着。
I just need to be alone.
-我送你回家。
- Let me take you home.
——不!
- No!
听着，你搞清楚了。
Look, you get this straight.
我不和警察约会，好吗?
I don't go out with cops, alright?
—名称为西科德。
- The name is Secord.
比利西。
Billy Secord.
我会和你保持联系的。
I'll be in touch.
基督-哦。
- Oh Christ.
-上帝啊，她真美。
- God is she beautiful.
-不不不不不
- No, no, no, no, no.
J "他说话那么疯狂，走路那么狂野J J "从没见过像他这样的人我-你好?
J“ he talks so crazy and he walks so wild j j“ never seen anything like him I - hello?
是的，她就在这里。
Yeah, she's right here.
很好。
Fine.
-抱歉，我要上有氧运动课。
- Sorry, I've got an aerobics class.
不，我不会告诉你它在哪的。
No, I'm not gonna tell you where it's at.
嘿，听着，你能不能别吵了，伙计?
Hey look, would you just lay off it buddy?
这是不可能的，对吧?
It's just not in the cards alright?
-你真是个好朋友
- What a friend you are.
嘿,克里斯蒂。
Hey christie.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is this?
你有这个来杀警察吗?
You got this to kill the cop with or something?
你知道，大多数人更喜欢枪。
Most people prefer guns you know.
-来吧，我们走。
- Come on, let's go.
我们要迟到了。
We're gonna be late.
一，二，三，四。
One, two, three, four.
踢。
Kick.
一，二，三，四。
One, two, three, four.
把你的腿抬上去，快点。
Get your legs up there, come on.
三,四。
Three, four.
你做的很好。
You're doing great.
使用这些武器。
Use those arms.
左边。
And to the left.
两个,三个。
Two, three.
你做得很好。
You're doing real good.
膝盖上下。
Knees up and down.
两个,三个。
Two, three.
四个和拉伸。
Four and stretch.
拉伸。
Stretch.
来吧，伙计们，我们走。
Come on you guys let's go.
拉伸。
Stretch.
和拉伸。
And stretch.
2、3、4。
Two, three, four.
现在很容易。
Now easy.
转折。
Twist.
两个。
Two.
用你的手臂。
Use your arms.
是的,继续前进。
Yeah, keep moving.
充满活力的家伙们。
Full of energy guys.
继续。
Keep going.
两个。
Two.
J "美体店J J "设定好时间和节奏J J美体店J J把那个美体珍珠出来好了，你们准备好了吗?
J“ body shop j j“ set the timing and the rhythm j j body shop j j make that body Pearl out j okay, are you guys ready?
是啊!
Yeah!
——手向前。
- Hands forward.
一边,一边。
And side, side.
向前,走了。
Forward, and go.
来吧，继续。
Come on, keep going.
我们几乎完成了。
We're almost finished.
踢，踢，踢。
And kick, kick, kick.
两个,三个。
Two, three.
现在我们试着逃跑。
Now we're trying running.
去,快。
Go, faster.
加油，伙计们。
Come on you guys.
得更快。
Faster.
让它燃烧!
Make it burn!
加油，伙计们。
Come on you guys.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
现在别停止。
Don't stop now.
我们几乎完成了。
We're almost finished.
来吧。
Come on.
你们做得很好。
You guys are doing great.
好吧!
Alright!
好吧。
Okay.
同学们，课上得不错。
Good class you guys.
四处走走。
Walk around a little bit.
伸展你的肌肉。
Stretch out those muscles.
洗澡前先冷静下来。
Cool down before you take shower.
再见。
See you all later.
你就是不打算辞职，是吗?
You're just not gonna quit are you?
-我就是那种固执的人。
- I'm just a stubborn kind of guy.
——没有开玩笑。
- No kidding.
-嘿，等一下
- Hey wait a minute.
你听说你发现的那具尸体是日本职业杀手吗?
Did you hear that guy you found dead was a professional Japanese assassin?
-你是说你大老远跑去上我的有氧运动课就为了告诉我这个?
- You mean you went all the way to my aerobics class just to tell me that?
-你还是不肯让我好过，是吗?
- You still won't make it easy will you?
——哦。
- Oh.
所以现在应该很容易了?
So now it should be easy?
-就这一次
- Just this once.
来点咖啡怎么样?
How about some coffee?
你知道咖啡对身体不好吗?
- You know coffee is really bad for your health?
不。
No.
不。不请,不。
No. No please, no.
别打扰我。
Leave me alone.
别打扰我。不。
Leave me alone. No.
嘿!
Hey!
加油，伙计们。
Come on you guys.
现在让她走吧!
Now let her go!
露西。不要让他们吓到你。
Go on Lucy. Don't let them scare you.
-有什么发现?
- What do we got?
-嘿，你以为你是谁?
- Hey, who the hell you think you are?
-是我让你别挡我的路。
- I'm the one telling you to get out of my way.
-或者我们把你留到甜点吃，好吗?
- Or maybe we just save you for desert yeah?
-你们真恶心!
- You guys are disgusting!
-不好意思!
- Well excuse me!
-别闹了!
- Knock it off!
-这本来是你的主意。
- Hey it was your idea in the first place.
-去死吧!
- Go to hell!
-嘿，去你的!
- Hey up yours!
嘿,看。
Hey look.
我们会成为朋友的，好吗?
We'll be friends alright?
我们去洗个澡。
We'll take a shower.
喝几杯啤酒……-把你的手拿开
Have a couple of beers... - Get your hands off of me!
——加油!
- Come on!
-你想要什么?
- What do you want?
-保持安静，动一动。
- Just keep quiet and move your butt.
你被捕了。
You're under arrest.
-听着，如果你要逮捕我，那就逮捕我。
- Look, if you're gonna book me, then book me.
否则就别再烦我了。
Otherwise just don't bother me anymore.
-我不会逮捕你的
- Oh I'm not gonna arrest you.
我只是想带你回我以前住的地方。
I just wanna take you back to my old neighborhood.
我想让你帮我揍一个人。
There's a guy there I want you to beat up for me.
-你能停车吗?
- Would you stop the car?
-得了吧。
- Oh come on.
我只是在逗你。
I'm only teasing you.
-停车!
- Stop the car!
-听着，克里斯蒂，我只是想帮忙。
- Look christie I'm only trying to help.
你会因为伤害那些人而被起诉。
You'd get charged for assault for what you did to those guys.
-那是我的问题。
- Well that's my problem.
我不需要任何帮助。
And I don't need any help.
尤其是你，西科德警官。
Especially from you, officer Secord.
-你知道吗，我听你说你不喜欢警察，真是烦透了。
- You know, I am sick and tired about hearing how you don't like cops.
因为我想告诉你，独立小姐。
Because I wanna tell you something, miss independence.
我喜欢当警察。
I like being a cop.
如果你因为我是警察而不想和我约会，那你就去死吧，女士。
And if you don't wanna go out with me just 'cause I'm a cop, then to hell with you, lady.
你现在可以走了。
You can go now.
——倾听。
- Listen.
我的公寓里没有咖啡。
I don't have any coffee in my apartment.
但我有v8果汁。
But I do have some v8 juice.
你愿意送我回家吗?
Would you like to take me home?
J，宝贝，看看我J，有些事我必须要知道J J，你是要和我一起冒险J J，还是只是一场走走停停的游戏J J，你要让我进去吗J
J baby take a look at me j j there's something that I've got to know j j are you gonna take a chance with me j j or just a game of stop and go j j are you gonna let me in j
J还是这将会是一个孤独的夜晚J J我们是否已经接近尾声了J J还是刚刚开始对的J J宝贝，看看我J J这张脸真的有那么糟糕吗J J也许你有了别人J
j or is it gonna be a lonely night j j are we getting near the end j j or just starting up right j j baby take a look at me j j is it really that bad a face j j maybe you've got someone else j
但也许我可以代替他我可以尽我最大的努力我喜欢你的睡衣。
j but maybe I could take his place j j I could give it my best shot j I like your pajamas.
-你在车里的表演真精彩。
- That was quite a show you put on in your car.
——我很抱歉。
- I'm sorry.
我不是故意这么生气的。
I didn't mean to get so angry.
——没关系。
- That's okay.
你生气的时候很性感。
You're very sexy when you get angry.
-哦,上帝!
- Oh god!
——克里斯蒂?
- Christie?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
——什么都没有。
- Nothing.
我就是睡不着。
I just couldn't sleep.
我做了个噩梦，所以我决定把衣服收起来。
I had a nightmare so I decided to put some clothes away.
-天啊，太美了。
- God, this is beautiful.
你从哪儿弄来的?
Where did you get this?
——这是日语。
- It's Japanese.
总有一天我会把它挂在墙上的。
One of these days I'm gonna hang it on my wall.
-你总是让人惊喜，不是吗?
- You're full of surprises aren't ya?
巴黎和奥斯陆在35号登机口进行最后的登机程序。
Paris and Oslo is in its final boarding process at gate 35.
-成为您的客人是我的荣幸。
- It is an honor to be your guest.
-这是我们的荣幸，山田三。
- The honor is ours, Yamada-San.
-我很感激你给我寄去日本的信。
- I'm grateful for the letter you sent me to Japan.
-有个坏消息，山田。
- We have bad news, Yamada-San.
不过我们以后再谈。
But we'll talk later.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
-我要取消今晚的约会。
- I gotta break our date tonight.
他们给了我下班后的工作。
They gave me off-duty work.
——没关系。
- That's okay.
-你还好吗?
- Are you alright?
听。
Listen.
我得把箱子送回去。
I gotta drive case back.
我晚点打给你，好吗?
I'll call you later okay?
——确定。
- Sure.
——再见。
- Bye.
-盯紧她
- Keep an eye on her.
——比利?
- Billy?
看在上帝的份上，你到底在哪里!
Where in the hell are you for Christ sakes!
-你怎么了?
- What's the matter with you?
-别说了，比利。
- Stop it Billy.
我只是觉得很奇怪。
It's just that I'm feeling really weird.
-快睡吧。
- Just go to sleep.
我明天早上就会到。
And I'll be there by morning.
——没关系。
- Never mind.
我会没事的。
I'll be okay.
你好好照顾自己就好。
You just take care of yourself.
上帝该死。
God dammit.
什么……
What the...
你的母亲!
You mother!
我要杀了你，狗娘养的!
I'll kill you, you son of a bitch!
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
什么……
What the...
不,不。
No, no.
不,请。
No, please.
不,不,谢谢。
No, no, please.
请。
Please.
-他们杀了他!
- They murdered him!
-比利，我觉得我有问题。
- Billy, I think there's something wrong with me.
我能在事情发生之前就感知到。
I can sense things before they even happen.
我在公寓里找东西。
I find things in the apartment.
我都不知道它们是从哪来的。
And I don't even know where they came from.
看看这个。
Look at this.
——耶稣!
- Jesus!
你怎么知道的?
How did you get that?
-我不记得了
- I don't remember.
-什么叫你不记得了?
- What do you mean you don't remember?
-我不记得了。
- I mean I don't remember.
我脑子一片空白好几个小时。
I go blank for hours.
甚至更长时间。
Maybe even longer.
我觉得有人在逼我做事。
I feel like there's somebody making me do things.
我不想做的事情。
Things that I don't wanna do.
-那就做点什么。
- Then do something about it.
-亲爱的，我不知道该怎么办。
- Honey, I don't know what to do.
-我会帮你的，宝贝。
- I'll help you sweetheart.
-医学上你是个很健康的年轻女人
- Medically you're a very fit young woman.
没有任何大脑异常的迹象。
No evidence of any abnormality in the brain.
没有肿瘤。
No tumor.
你有一颗坚强的心。
You have a strong heart.
你的饮食比一般人好。
Your diet is better than average.
当然，你的压力很大。
You are under severe stress of course.
但除此之外，boland医生，你看的那个精神病医生，说没有什么异常。
But otherwise, doctor boland, the psychiatrist you saw, says there's nothing out of the ordinary.
除了你特殊的感官知觉。
Aside from your exceptional extra sensory perception.
还有你对日本文化的痴迷。
And your pre-occupation with Japanese culture.
这没什么坏处。
No harm in that.
——请问?
- Excuse me?
你看到西科德警官了吗?
Have you seen officer Secord?
-不，我没有。
- No I haven't.
-好吧，我们就看看是谁让我这么做的。
- Oh well, we'll just see who put me up to it.
我们要和你一起去吗?
So are we going with you?
-你知道我真正想做什么吗?
- You know what I really want to do?
我想坐警车去。
I wanna go in a police car.
我也是，我也是!
- Me too, me too!
我能打开警笛和警灯吗?
Can I put on the siren and the lights?
-马上就把我打倒了。
- Shot me down right away.
- - - - - -来吧。——好吧,好吧!
- Come on. - Okay, okay!
-我去拿。
- I'll get it.
你们就坐在那里。
You guys just sit there.
这是谁呢?
Who could this be?
这是疯狂的。
This is crazy.
哦,嗨。
Oh hi.
进来吧。
Come on in.
我们还需要一些毛巾。
We could use some more towels.
哦很热。
Ooh it's hot.
不要拉我。
Don't pull me.
这感觉很好。
This feels good.
我们玩得很开心!
We've been having fun!
——她是谁?
- Who's she?
我不知道。
I don't know.
但它是好的。
But it's alright.
-你最好小心点，大个子!
- You better watch yourself big man!
这到底是个什么地方?
What the hell kind of place is this?
-滚开，婊子!
- Beat it bitch!
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
呀。
Jeez.
来吧孩子。
Go ahead kid.
那狗娘养的归你了。
The son of bitch is all yours.
-我们走吧。-不，我想看
- Oh let's split. - No, I wanna watch.
-这家伙真是个混蛋。-你说对了。
- This guy is a real jerk. - Boy, you said it.
-我们走吧。
- Let's get outta here.
她对他做了什么?
What is she doing to him?
-我不知道。
- I don't know.
但那个混蛋似乎很享受，不是吗?
But the bastard seems to be enjoying it doesn't he?
——确定。
- Sure is.
他怎么了?
What's the matter with him?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
——不!
- No!
——克里斯蒂?
- Christie?
克里斯蒂?
Christie?
你到底去哪儿了?
Where the hell have you been?
我到处找你。
I looked everywhere for you.
克里斯蒂?
Christie?
这是怎么回事?
What is going on?
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
-我不知道。
- I don't know.
-你得知道。
- You gotta know.
你中午就走了。
You've been gone since noon.
-比利，我不管这些医生怎么说。
- Billy, I don't care what these doctors say.
我有问题。
There's something wrong with me.
我试着与它抗争。
I try to fight it.
但我都不记得是什么了。
But I can't even remember what.
或者为什么。
Or why.
有个人,比利。
There's somebody, Billy.
我能感觉到它就在房间里，有时就在我身边。
I can feel it in the room sometimes near me.
——倾听。
- Listen.
有个军官在亚洲分部。
There's an officer in the asiatic division.
他告诉我市中心有个日本人很崇拜的人。
He told me there's this guy downtown the local Japanese swear by.
-告诉你，比利，我不相信魔鬼、鬼魂、灵魂之类的东西。
- For your information, Billy, I don't believe in demons, ghosts, spirits, or any of that kind of stuff.
-我也不知道
- Well neither do I.
但当你失去记忆时，我们不知道该相信什么，不是吗?
But when you blank out, we don't know what to believe in do we?
-比利，我不认为这是个好主意。
- Billy, I don't think this is such a good idea.
——冥界。我叫比利·西科德。
- Hel. Lo - my name is Billy Secord.
我们通过电话。
We spoke on the phone.
-哦，是的，你在等着。
- Oh yes, you are expected.
请跟我来好吗?
Would you follow me?
-年轻人啊，你们来是明智的。
- It is wise of you to come, oh young ones.
他现在在这里。
He is here now.
我可以告诉你更多。
I can tell you much more.
来了。
Come.
跟我来。
Follow me.
-肯定比洛基恐怖片强多了。
- Sure beats the rocky horror picture show.
-给他个机会。
- Give him a chance.
-这些都是必要的。
- These are necessary.
以防幽灵生气。
In case the spirit becomes angry.
-他都不问问我有什么问题吗?
- Isn't he even gonna ask me what the problem is?
——我们只想放松一下。
- Just relax.
-退后，离开她
- Move back, leave her.
-别担心，甜心。
- Don't worry sweetheart.
我就在这里。
I'll be right here.
现在请回答。
Please answer now.
他在你身体里吗?
Is he in you?
——是的。
- Yes.
他是。
He is.
他想让你停下来!
And he wants you to stop!
-你是谁?
- Who are you?
-天啊。
- Oh my god.
-也许我们最好停下来。
- Maybe we better stop.
——没有。
- No.
你完成它。
You finish it.
把这狗娘养的弄走。
Get rid of the son of a bitch.
-我不知道怎么了。
- I don't know what is wrong.
-你在干什么?
- What are you doing?
-我必须服从神灵。
- I must obey the spirit.
他希望我放了她。
He wishes me to cut her loose.
——不!
- No!
-不，不，不要。
- No, no, don't.
停止。
Stop.
请原谅他。
Please forgive him.
那个傻瓜不知道他正在犯一个多么可怕的错误。
The fool does not know what a terrible mistake he's making.
帮帮我!
Help me!
哦，比利，帮帮我!
Oh Billy, help me!
我很害怕!
I'm scared!
你这个傻瓜!
You fool!
你阻止不了我!
You cannot stop me!
我是忍者!
I am a ninja!
没有人，没有什么能阻止我!
No one, nothing can stop me!
他走了。
He is gone.
-你确定吗?
- Are you sure?
-他自己也累了。
- He's tired himself.
但他会回来的。
But he will return.
-我不能说。
- I cannot say.
-我想知道他是谁
- I wanna know who he is.
-我不能再告诉你了。
- I cannot tell you any more.
-我听到了“忍者”。
- I heard "ninja".
我想知道那是什么鬼东西。
I wanna know what the hell that is.
你最好不要知道太多。
It is better if you not know too much.
为了你自己。
For your own sake.
-你说呢，老混蛋
- You tell me, you old bastard.
不然我现在就抓你。
Or I'm gonna bust you right now.
-她被一个黑色忍者附身了。
- She is possessed by a black ninja.
拥有九人之手的所有力量。
With all the powers of the nine hand cutting.
什么也做不了。
Nothing can be done.
我告诉你她会完全…-别告诉我什么都做不了!
I tell you she will be totally... - Don't tell me nothing can be done!
我要你帮她!
I want you to help her!
——对不起。
- Sorry.
我不能。
I cannot.
有一件事。
There is one thing.
——什么?
- What?
-在日本的鹰山。
- In the eagle mountain in Japan.
唯一能摧毁他的力量。
The very one power that can destroy him.
——日本。
- Japan.
-只有忍者才能摧毁忍者。
- Only a ninja can destroy a ninja.
——冻结!
- Freeze!
——嘿!原谅我。
- Hey! Excuse me.
你是谁?
Who are you?
-我们能帮你吗?-你怎么进来的?
- Can we help you? - How'd you get in here?
-你要告诉我发生了什么吗?
- So are you gonna tell me what happened?
-他把你催眠了，仅此而已。
- He hypnotized you that's all.
-那这些伤痕是怎么回事?
- So why all the bruises?
比利。
Come on Billy.
你可以告诉我。
You can tell me.
-我觉得他不知道自己在做什么。
- I don't think he knew what he was doing.
那家伙可能是个骗子。
The guy's probably a fake.
-你有事瞒着我。
- There's something you're not telling me.
-最近怎么样?
- How's it going?
——克里斯蒂?
- Christie?
——我很抱歉。
- I'm sorry.
-马蒂·温斯洛。
- Marty winslow.
匹克威克中士，这是克里斯蒂。
Sergeant pickwick, this is christie.
-我知道这位女士很漂亮。
- I know the lady's beautiful.
但别忘了葬礼。
But don't forget the funeral.
四点半，克拉克市公墓。
4:30, Clark city cemetery.
-是的，我尽量去。
- Yeah, I'll try and make it.
新东西吗?
Anything new?
——什么都没有。
- Nothing.
我只是猜测这些谋杀案与我们上周在高尔夫球场浪费的职业杀手有关。
Just speculation the killings are linked to that professional assassin we wasted at the golf course last week.
-你找到的那具尸体，是从停尸房偷出来的。
- That stiff you found, it was stolen out of the morgue.
现在局长认为这是一项专业工作。
Now the chief believes it's a professional job.
日本黑手党之类的。
Some sort of Japanese mafia or something.
所以要小心。
So be careful.
四点半见。
See you at 4:30.
-不，你没有。
- No you don't.
又不是。
Not again.
该死的你!
Damn you!
别烦我!
Just leave me alone!
停止它!
Stop it!
我每天都梦到你我什么都不想
J I dream about you all the time j j I can't think about nothing else j
——不!
- No!
-我们一起分享大卫的诗篇。
- And we share together the psalm of David.
诗篇23。
Psalm 23.
耶和华是我的牧者。我不需要。
The lord is my Shepherd. I shall not want.
他让我躺在绿色的牧场上。
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
他领我在可安歇的水边。
He leads me beside quiet waters.
他恢复了我的灵魂。
He restores my soul.
他为自己的名引导我走义路。
He guides me in the paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
我虽行过死荫的幽谷，也不怕遭害，因为你与我同在。
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death I will fear no evil for thou art with me.
你的杖，你的竿，都安慰我。
Thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.
在我仇敌面前，你为我摆设筵席。
Thou has prepared a table before me in the presence of mine enemies.
你用油抹了我的头。
Thou has anointed my head with oil.
我的杯子溢出。
My cup overflows.
当然，善良和仁爱将伴随我一生的所有日子。
Surely goodness and loving kindness will follow me all of the days of my life.
我必住在耶和华的殿中，直到永远。
And I will dwell in the house of the lord forever.
地和其中所充满的，都属乎耶和华。
The earth is the lord's and all it contains.
警惕。
On guard.
敬礼。
Salute.
学员。
Cadets.
给我把枪，谁给我把枪!
- Give me a gun, somebody give me a gun!
-打开后备箱。
- Open that trunk.
给我一根指挥棒。
Give me a Baton.
——我也是。
- Me too.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
来吧。
Come on.
——抓住它!-他在这里!
- Hold it! - He's over here!
打击他了!
Blow him away!
他在那里!
He's up there!
给我们一些支持!
Give us some support!
快上来!
Come on up here!
-过来!-让他尝尝吧!
- Come over here! - Let him have it!
看到他了吗?
See him over there?
——冻结!——抓住它!
- Freeze! - Hold it!
——传播他们!
- Spread 'em!
-让我跟他谈谈
- Let me talk to him.
——移动它。
- Move it.
-我得问问…-我在等你。
- I have to ask... - I was waiting for you.
-你认识我?
- You know me?
-你知道剑在哪里吗?
- You know where the sword is?
——也许。
- Maybe.
-不要犹豫。
- Do not hesitate.
我是从日本来复仇的。
I have come from Japan to revenge.
我知道该怎么做。
I know what should be done.
-你是忍者!
- You're a ninja!
-没关系。
- It doesn't matter.
去把那女孩和那把剑带来，把他们带到古庙去。
Go and get the girl and the sword, and take them to the old temple.
在小山丘上。
On the hill.
等待我。
Wait for me.
别担心。
Don't worry.
-嗨。
- Hey.
嘿,查理。
Hey Charlie.
嘿，这是怎么回事?
Hey what's going on here?
-他们只是在睡觉。
- They are only sleeping.
-比利，你吓到我了
- Billy, you scared me.
天啊，真高兴你来了……——不要动。
God, I'm so glad you're here... - Don't move.
-你在干什么?
- What are you doing?
-我说了别动。
- I said just don't move.
他们都死了，克里斯蒂。
They're all dead christie.
你杀了他们。
You killed them.
我看到了一切。
I saw everything.
-我没杀过人。
- I haven't killed anybody.
-听我说。
- Listen to me.
这里有一个日本人。
There's a man here from Japan.
一个忍者。
A ninja.
我们要去山上的古庙见他。
We're gonna go meet him at that old temple on the hill.
他会帮你的。
And he is going to help you.
我不能……——不要动!
I can't... - Don't move!
-我永远不会做任何伤害你的事。
- I could never do anything to hurt you.
-天啊，我希望这是真的。
- Oh god I hope that's true.
把你的手放在前面。
Put your hands out in front of you.
——但比利…-把你的手放在前面!
- But Billy... - Put your hands out in front of you!
-我爱你。
- I love you.
——克里斯蒂。
- Christie no.
克里斯蒂。
Christie no.
现在醒来。
Wake up now.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
该死的!
Damn!
-你是忍者。
- You're the ninja.
你能帮我吗?
You can help me?
——是的。
- Yes.
-只有忍者才能摧毁忍者，这是真的吗?
- Is it true that only a ninja can destroy a ninja?
——这是真的。
- It's true.
-请帮帮我。
- Help me please.
我必须摆脱他。
I must get rid of him.
-你知道我必须做什么吗?
- Do you know what I must do?
-做你该做的。
- Do what you have to.
我不想再伤害任何人。
I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
-可能对你有危险。
- It might be dangerous for you.
-我会死吗?
- Will I die?
-如果灵魂离开你就不会。
- Not if the spirit leaves you.
然后回到他的身体。
And returns to his body.
那我就毁了他。
Then I will destroy him.
这样你就安全了。
And you will be safe.
-如果不行，你会杀了我。
- And if it doesn't, you'll kill me.
克里斯蒂。
Come on christie.
来吧。
Come on.
——比利?
- Billy?
我想我现在会好起来的。
I think I'm gonna be alright now.
-我爱你!
- Oh I love you!
-我爱你。
- I love you.
比利等。
Billy wait.
克里斯蒂-不!
- Christie no!
-现在结束了。
- It's over now.